[CROWD CHEERS]
- THIS SONG IS NOT A
REBEL SONG
- THIS SONG IS SUNDAY
BLOODY SUNDAY
[CROWD CHEERS]
[DRUMS PLAY]
♪♪♪
♪ OHHHHHH OHHHHHHH ♪
♪ I CAN'T BELIEVE THE
NEWS TODAY ♪
♪ OH, I CAN'T CLOSE MY EYES AND
MAKE IT GO AWAY ♪
♪ HOW LONG, HOW LONG MUST WE
SING THIS SONG? ♪
♪ HOW LONG? HOW LONG? ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TONIGHT ♪
♪ WE CAN BE AS ONE ♪
♪ TONIGHT ♪
♪ BROKEN BOTTLES UNDER
CHILDREN'S FEET ♪
♪ BODIES STREWN ACROSS THE
DEAD-END STREET ♪
♪ BUT I WON'T HEED THE
BATTLE CALL ♪
♪ IT PUTS MY BACK UP, PUTS MY
BACK UP AGAINST THE WALL ♪
♪ SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY ♪
♪ ALRIGHT, LET'S GO ♪
♪ AND THE BATTLE'S JUST BEGUN ♪
♪ THERE'S MANY LOST, BUT TELL ME
WHO HAS WON? ♪
♪ THE TRENCHES DUG WITHIN
OUR HEARTS ♪
♪ AND MOTHERS, CHILDREN,
BROTHERS, SISTERS TORN APART ♪
♪ SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY ♪
♪ HOW LONG, HOW LONG MUST WE
SING THIS SONG? ♪
♪ HOW LONG? HOW LONG? ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TONIGHT WE CAN BE AS
ONE, TONIGHT ♪
♪ TONIGHT, TONIGHT ♪
♪ ALRIGHT, LET'S GO ♪
♪♪♪
- HOLD IT UP,
LET IT FLY
- SING NO MORE
- SING (NO MORE) SING NO MORE
- NO MORE (NO MORE) NO MORE (NO
MORE) NO MORE (NO MORE) NO MORE
(NO MORE)
♪NO MORE WIPE YOUR TEARS AWAY ♪
♪ WIPE THE TEARS AWAY ♪
♪ WIPE YOUR BLOODSHOT EYES ♪
♪ WIPE YOUR TEARS AWAY
(SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY) ♪
♪ (SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY) ♪
♪ SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY ♪
♪ SHHHH (SUNDAY, BLOODY
SUNDAY) SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY ♪
- I'M SO SICK OF IT
♪ AND IT'S TRUE WE ARE IMMUNE ♪
♪ WHEN FACT IS FICTION AND
TV REALITY ♪
♪ AND TODAY THE MILLIONS CRY♪
♪ WE EAT AND DRINK WHILE
TOMORROW THEY DIE ♪
♪ THE REAL BATTLE JUST BEGUN
(SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY) ♪
♪ TO CLAIM THE VICTORY JESUS WON
♪ ON SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY ♪
♪ SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY ♪
[CROWD CHEERS]
[DRUMS]
[MUSIC RESUMES]
♪ SUNDAY, BLOODY SUNDAY ♪
♪♪♪
[CROWD CHEERS]